<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Matomo as a Platform on</title><link>https://druloloy.github.io/quartz/</link><description>Recent content in Matomo as a Platform on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://druloloy.github.io/quartz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Data Collection</title><link>https://druloloy.github.io/quartz/notes/Data-Collection/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://druloloy.github.io/quartz/notes/Data-Collection/</guid><description>Matomo tracks the following by default:
User IP address (see also: IP anonymisation) Optional User ID Date and time of the request Title of the page being viewed (Page Title) URL of the page being viewed (Page URL) URL of the page that was viewed prior to the current page (Referrer URL) Screen resolution being used Time in local user’s timezone Files that were clicked and downloaded ( Download) Links to an outside domain that were clicked ( Outlink) Pages generation time (the time it takes for webpages to be generated by the webserver and then downloaded by the user: Page speed) Location of the user: country, region, city, approximate latitude and longitude ( Geolocation) Main Language of the browser being used (Accept-Language header) User Agent of the browser being used (User-Agent header) Some information is also stored in first party cookies and then collected by Matomo:</description></item><item><title>Features</title><link>https://druloloy.github.io/quartz/notes/Features/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://druloloy.github.io/quartz/notes/Features/</guid><description>Web Analytics Features Real time data updates
Watch real time flow of visits to your website. Get a detailed view of your visitors, pages they have visited and goals they have triggered.</description></item><item><title>Installation</title><link>https://druloloy.github.io/quartz/notes/Installation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://druloloy.github.io/quartz/notes/Installation/</guid><description>Pre-installation Process Before we start the installation, open the server using SSH.
1 $ ssh forge@192.168.1.1 Replace the 192.</description></item><item><title>Pricing</title><link>https://druloloy.github.io/quartz/notes/Pricing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://druloloy.github.io/quartz/notes/Pricing/</guid><description>Matomo offfers 19 EU or 21 USD per month when hosted on their servers (Cloud). Matomo can also be installed on our servers for free (On-Premise), however we&amp;rsquo;ll have limited features compared to Cloud-hosted.</description></item><item><title>Pros and Cons</title><link>https://druloloy.github.io/quartz/notes/Pros-and-Cons/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://druloloy.github.io/quartz/notes/Pros-and-Cons/</guid><description>Pros
Accessibility: Matomo is available on both Android and iOS platforms, making it easily accessible for users on various devices.</description></item><item><title>Reports</title><link>https://druloloy.github.io/quartz/notes/Reports/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://druloloy.github.io/quartz/notes/Reports/</guid><description>These are the reports that Matomo can generate:
Dashboard A/B Testing Acquisition and Marketing Channels Behaviour Cohorts Content Tracking Ecommerce Event Tracking Form Analytics Funnels Goals and Conversions Heatmaps Media Analytics Multi Channel Conversion Attribution Page Overlay Page Transitions Real-time reports SEO Web Vitals Session Recordings Site Search User IDs Users Flow Visitors Navigation Data Collection Features Installation Pricing Pros and Cons Reports Requirements and Recommendations Self-Hosted Limitations</description></item><item><title>Requirements and Recommendations</title><link>https://druloloy.github.io/quartz/notes/Requirements-and-Recommendations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://druloloy.github.io/quartz/notes/Requirements-and-Recommendations/</guid><description>Minimum Requirements Webserver such as Apache, Nginx, IIS, LiteSpeed, etc. Matomo 4.x requires PHP version 7.2.5 or greater. Matomo fully works with PHP 8 as well.</description></item><item><title>Self-Hosted Limitations</title><link>https://druloloy.github.io/quartz/notes/Self-Hosted-Limitations/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://druloloy.github.io/quartz/notes/Self-Hosted-Limitations/</guid><description>These features don&amp;rsquo;t come in free for self-hosted solution.
Activity Log WooCommerce Analysis Search Engine Keywords Performance Funnels Users Flow White Label Heatmap &amp;amp; Session Recording A/B Testing Custom Reports Forms Media Analytics Roll Up Reporting Advertising Conversion Export SEO Web Vitals Multi-Channel Conversion Attribution Cohorts SAML Integration Matomo offers these features for different prices each and can be paid annually, see [[https://matomo.</description></item></channel></rss>